Hey! Is Miyama Kirishima gonna show or what?
He's not.
I'm telling you, he's not headed this way.
I told Shiota Nao to bring Kirishima and
Somei Yoshino to a warehouse I'm renting.
Which is also where I sent
the thugs you guys brought.
Though I have my doubts about
how much use they'll be...
Who do you think you are, you little shit?
Considering you spent a month in the
hospital with broken teeth and bones,
you're nowhere near as
intimidating as you think.
You little—
Hey. Pipe down.
If you don't like it, you can
head back to Tokyo right now.
Dammit...
I've got the hotel Miyama is
staying at under surveillance.
There's been no movement there
since Shiota Nao went inside.
I told her to bring him
to the warehouse by 10PM.
If there's no movement by 9PM, then
we'll have someone crash his room.
But when you do grab him, don't kill him.
Save that kind of thing for
when I'm not around. Got it?
This entire harassment campaign is only
because you guys won't shut up about
settling this score with him.
And since I'm footing the
bill, we do things my way.
Azami just got to Osaka.
Drop by later and give your regards.
That explains it.
To Be Honest, I Want to Marry You Part One
I wasn't sure why they wanted
anything with me before...
But I recognize the curly-haired punk
that I knocked out in the club.
Die, asshole!
They're the gang members that
Akaza Shiori hired, right?
They must hate us pretty bad
to travel all this way.
What are you doing there, Yoshino?
You wanna know?
If possible.
It's pretty simple: after I traded
contact info with Shiota Nao,
I set my sights on an apartment building
in Kobe that Ozu Kento is staying at.
Where we going?
Kobe.
You knew he had a place in Kobe, right?
How did you learn about it?
That comes later. So, what's your move?
You wanna head to the spot
Ozu Kento specified?
It's probably crawling with goons
who are ready to kill you.
Ozu's a spoiled little rich boy,
so he probably paid for them.
If we take him down first,
the rest are just a bunch of rabble.
And if you come to where I am,
there's only four guys to deal with.
That sounds doable for you.
We're leaving.
Get dressed.
There's Ozu Kento, the gang
members from before, and...
A guy with red hair and a perm.
Looks kinda like a host.
Hey!
Say that again?
A guy with red hair and a
perm who looks like a host?
Yoshino, I can take it from here.
Out of those four, only Ozu Kento
doesn't know what you look like.
Would you please go home right now,
before they recognize you?
Ozu wouldn't recognize me?
I've been making sure that pics
of you don't start circulating.
Dude, are you for real?
Still, good to know.
It is?
Kirishima...
You're gonna do exactly what I tell you to.
Somei Yoshino
Found Ozu Kento.
I'm gonna trail him.
I'm on the way.
Where are you now?
Number Withheld
Hello there. This is Kirishima.
How the hell do you have my number?
I never expected I'd end up
having to use it, I assure you.
Would you get to the point, you little shit?
Well, Yoshino and I have gotten
wrapped up in a bit of trouble...
There's a karaoke club called Albatross
in the western district, room 211...
I've got her hiding there.
I just sent you the directions.
I've got business to attend to, so would
you mind picking her up right away?
You know what's gonna happen
to you if she's hurt, right?
You're gonna pray for death.
Sounds lovely.
I've recently started thinking I'd
be better off with you dead.
Let's mark that down for later, shall we?
Now, get to it.
Hey!
He and the girl apparently just left
the hotel and got into a taxi.
Tell your boys to follow them.
Do not lose sight of that cab.
Hey!
I'm going for a smoke.
Let me know if anything happens.
Got it. So you want me to meet up
with the guys watching Miyama?
Ugh, what a drag.
See ya, Junior.
It's good to see you again.
Let's wrap this up fast
and head back to Tokyo.
I'm honestly not sure why you're willing
to do all this for these no-name punks...
But getting dragged into
their stupid revenge...
especially considering
the cost, I'm not a fan.
I-I mean, I'll make sure it gets done,
since you're the one asking...
Creepy.
Oh! Ozu-kun?
It is you! Do you remember me?
Uh, so you're Suzuki Mai-chan?
Yep, that's me. Suzuki, fourth-year at Houyou U.
You don't remember me?
We met at an inter-school social last year...
but I guess there were
a lot of people there.
Uh, sorry. If I'm being honest,
I don't remember.
I left partway through, so...
What are you doing in Osaka,
Suzuki-san? Traveling?
Nah. My family lives down
here, so I'm visiting.
Huh, is that right?
Have I met this girl before?
Posts
Following
Suzuki Mai
4th Year
Follow
This account is not public.
I found an account that
seems to match her, but...
Could Miyama Kirishima have sent her?
Nah...
If he knew where I was, he
would've shown up in person.
Her face isn't my style, but...
I'll have a gin and tonic and...
how about you?
Oh, sorry, do you not drink?
Not exactly, but...
Just a few drinks. Come on.
In that case... just one.
Karaoke Albatross
I hate this. What is even going on?
Hey! Let go! Where are we going?!
We would've been in danger at the hotel,
so we need to go somewhere else.
I think where we're headed should be safe.
"Should be"?!
You'll need to be patient and wait there.
Someone will show up, but
I put a phone in your bag,
so if they ask you where I am,
just hand it to them.
They'll understand if you tell them
it's synced to Yoshino's GPS.
No!
I already told you where to find Ozu!
This has nothing to do with me anymore!
You're right.
I really should have blocked your account
the second I noticed it in Yoshino's phone.
You've done nothing wrong.
So, please... stop talking for a second.
This sucks.
I hope I never see him again!
Who the hell're you?
You one of his chicks?
H-His...?
Y-You mean Miyama Kirishima?
H-Here!
He said to give it to you.
If you're looking for him,
take this and find him!
I have nothing to do with all this!
You're comin' too.
Come on, let go! I really
don't know anything!
Who're you supposed to be?
And where the hell is Miyama Kirishima?
I asked you where Miyama
Kirishima is, asshole.
Hey, go watch the entrance.
He left the chick behind and ran.
Right.
And call Ozu.
Kirishima is probably gonna
meet up with Somei Yoshino.
Once she's found, take care of her!
That son of a bitch thinks
he can screw around—
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Keep her name outta your
filthy mouth, dumbass.
You wanna die?
Asshole—
Son of a bitch!
Bastard...
You think you're hot shit, you—
Ew, I touched his hair.
Huh, are you Shiota Nao?
You're super cute! How about
we grab a bite sometime?
Come on.
Hey, big guy! I get the silent treatment?
I'm looking for someone.
Are you Miyama Kirishima?
Fuck off, curly.
You think these curls are natural?
I obviously got it styled this
way on purpose, dumbass!
I don't give a shit,
you frizzy-lookin' jackass!
Shochu my ass! This is basically juice!
Non-alcoholic
Excuse me, mister, can I get another
two buckwheat shochu on the rocks?
You're still good to drink, right, Ozu-kun?
Uh... I might be hitting my limit.
What? It was your idea to drink! Come on!
Oh, I was wanting to try the red.
Let me order that too!
Drink this, 'kay?
Sorry, let me just run to the bathroom.
What is it?
Hey! Where the fuck are you?!
Don't scream!
Miyama contacted us.
He ditched the broad and
left the karaoke place!
He even sent us a map!
Hey, have all the guys at the
warehouse join up with us!
I told you not to make moves like that!
Screw you! We're tired of taking
orders from a pissant like you!
Fuck off!
Dammit, where the hell did he go?!
Pay the damn tab!
Miyama Kirishima
Cell Phone
Hello, Yoshino?
Where exactly are you now?!
Just left the karaoke place.
I'm still in the city.
I told you to do what I said, dammit!
I know, and I appreciate that.
You were right, the corner room on the
second floor of that karaoke place...
There was a window behind the TV which
made it easy to drop onto a back street.
And what I told you to do...
Was to ditch your tail and then meet
up with me with Shiota Nao!
You did something else, didn't you?!
I had Ozu Kento right where I
wanted him, but he just took off!
And where's Shiota Nao?
She was kind of in the way, so I
left her at the karaoke place.
I had Toriashi-san pick her up,
so it should be fine.
You dragged Shoma into this?!
Well, I don't know anyone
else in Osaka, so...
He didn't seem happy about it, but he
was the only one who came to mind.
If you keep screwing with him,
he will actually kill you.
Why did you have
to mess with everything?
We could've resolved this my way.
I'm sorry. But if I had gone to Ozu,
the guys tailing me would've gotten near you.
If you had gotten hurt, this
would all be for nothing.
That's exactly what I've been trying
to avoid for the last month.
Yoshino, I'm begging you, please go home.
I don't know how you
learned about Ozu Kento,
but the idea of you being out
there alone... I'm so worried.
The hell do you care what I
get up to in my hometown?
I was wonderin' why you
were sneakin' around,
and then I found out you and this Ozu dude
aren't just creepin' around
here but in Kobe too...
How do you know about that, Yoshino?
Dumbass. You two seem to have forgotten,
but this ain't Tokyo, it's Osaka, got it?!
Yet you waltz in here and
make a mess of things...
And I'm bettin' it ain't the kind of
thing you'd quit, even if I told you to.
Well, if you're dead set on whatever
it is, then don't get found out.
You gotta operate like you're
ready to kill everybody.
And if you can't manage that, then the
least can do is die where you stand!
I'll foot the bill to
dispose of you all after.
Once the bodies are gone, then it's over.
And if you don't like that, then take your
ass back to Tokyo, and never come back.
That way, the moment we hang
up, I am done with you!
You hear me?!
You know, there's something I meant
to tell you today at the aquarium...
Where is this comin' from?
My birthday is November 13th.
Wh-What are we talkin' about?
I really am a Scorpio. And as of
November 13th, I'll be 18.
Your... birthday...?
I've never told anybody.
I've never really thought about
what kind of food I prefer,
but I like dining with you the best.
I don't really have any hobbies, but if
you do, I'd like to join you for them.
Seriously, what are you...?
I'm saying, once I turn 18,
why don't we get married?
You're seriously asking this now?!
This just confirmed it.
I'm the only one who can marry you.
And there's no woman who
can marry me but you.
You are so insane that
it's almost impressive...
Who the hell would be like,
"Yes, I'd love to," at a time like this?
Well, because it'd be
impossible for anyone else.
I love you more than anyone
else in the world.
And I'm sure that if you tried to be
with anyone else, it wouldn't work out.
I guarantee it.
Are you pickin' a fight with me?
Never. But I'm willing to bet my life on it.
Dumbass. You really think I wanna
take that kinda gamble with a dude
who might be about to die anyway?
Well, it's 9:46 right now...
If I can wrap this up before
tomorrow, then I win.
How about it?
I'm talking about a bet.
If I die or it takes a second
after midnight, then I lose.
I won't say a word about wanting
to get married ever again.
But if I do manage to take care of this
and make Ozu Kento pay before that time...
Let's see...
How about you make me your boyfriend?
Getting married right away is off the
table, but we can do that, at least.
For stipulations, maybe we can't
break up before we both graduate?
Like I'd agree to that, dumbass.
Huh, you're more timid
than I imagined, Yoshino.
That ain't what I meant!
Why the hell am I gonna make a gamble
on some beef you got into on your own?
If this is a bet between you and me,
it oughta be you or me
who's the winner, right?
You manage to take care of
all this before tomorrow,
and then beat me on top of it, then
I'll date you or whatever you want.
You know just what to say, Yoshino.
Now I'm really motivated.
So, how exactly do I beat you?
Feel free to set the terms.
Y'know, stupid, all this depends on
you survivin' in the first place.
You're on your own, right?
You sure you've got a chance?
Want me to find a spot to
help you fight one-on-one?
Not that I'm sure there's
any place like that, but...
Don't worry. I've already found it.